[{"answer": "CHWARZENEGGER: Well, you know, I always have been very successful in my professional life.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "What has it been like to be you in the last year?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "You know, I never tell the press what to write and what to say.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Have you felt -- have you felt it's been too much or not?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I would say I don't read any of it.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "And you're probably not reading half of it, right, I would imagine?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "I think that there's a tremendous amount of people that have shown great support, and then there's a lot of people that have let me know that they're disappointed and it's perfectly fine, including my children that were disappointed in that action and inevitably my wife was very disappointed, and so, it's -- look, it's my -- it's my fault.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "And who's been -- who's been the rocks, if you like, for you in this?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "I cannot speak for Maria.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Do you think there is a good chance you can get back together?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "I would say that it makes no difference.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Was it more that?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I think the book goes into the details of the whole thing and I think that people, when they read it, they will get an understanding of what the whole thing was about, and that I leave it at that.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "What was the reality of that?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Could I see her, please?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Look, it may take awhile.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Where is she?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "CHWARZENEGGER: Well, you know, I have really no interest to go and run for office or anything like that.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Or is that now like the bodybuilding, done?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, let me just tell you that I didn't care what it takes in order to fix the state.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Was it harder than you thought, being governor?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "I think that, you know, with debates, the most important thing is to be real.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "What's your advice?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, as you know, John F. Kennedy came from a very rich family.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Are you surprised that in America, the country that gave you the opportunity to become what you are, that they would now turn on somebody for being what used to be the great American dream?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "I would have to first listen to the debates.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "I know you haven't decided who you're going to vote for in all this time, but right now, if you had to vote tomorrow, who would you vote for?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "It's very important.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "So they're that important to you?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "We maybe would have done things a little differently, but I can guarantee you that the president is doing everything that he can to solve the problems.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "I mean how -- what do you think?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I think that I had the most extraordinary talent in visualizing.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "When you go back to that little boy, Arnold Schwarzenegger, what was it about you, do you think, that gave you the drive to achieve all this?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I cannot do the 400 pound stuff anymore.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Can you still do the 400 pound stuff?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I lift every day.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "What's the most you lift these days?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Maybe is a different thing, yes.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Your idea of light weight and mine are probably two different things, aren't they?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "I still am lifting with 150, 200 pounds.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "What is your idea of a light weight these days?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Five hundred sit ups and leg raises.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "How many sit ups?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I ride the bicycle every day for an hour.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Wait a minute, 500 sit ups, really?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "CHWARZENEGGER: Whatever the director says.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "If you all got in a room together and had a fight, the Expendables, who would win?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I think that it was a great idea to do the book.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Was it something that you felt by the time you closed the last chapter and finished and read it through, you were glad you had done it, even though you may get criticized from certain quarters?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I would just say sorry for what I've done.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "If Maria's watching this, and she might well be watching this, what would you say to her?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I think everyone deserves to be forgiven and get a break.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "You think -- do you deserve to be forgiven, do you think?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "That's why I wrote the book.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Most Catholics are in recovery, aren't they?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "It lasted about three or four years.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "So how long did the Nun thing really last in reality?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I did mass in my house, literally, (inaudible)", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "What a perfect pair, I would think.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "How you going to feel if your book, \"Bad Habits, Confessions,\" being next to Arnold Schwarzenegger's book on the book stands?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Close.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Impregnated their housekeepers?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "CCARTHY: No, I don't, only because I've learned in my own -- how do I put it -- risky words I've used in my career to question people and make statements, it's -- I can't even go into politics.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Do you have any view of the election, talking of bad habits?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I am so single.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "For any men watching, you are single, right?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Are you on the hunt?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Little beady eye?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "You brought him up pretty much on your own, right?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "121002pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 506}]